{
    "question": "6 in they read a book under a tree?    Yes\r\na. They are\r\nh. They wers\r\nc. They will\r\nd. They do\r\n7. We can buy ruler in the\r\na. Stationery store\r\nb. Candy store\r\ne. Electronic store\r\nd. Music store\r\n8. Rama: Look at these shoes, Lita,\r\nThey are very nice\r\nLita : Yes?\r\nRama ninety nine thousand rupiah\r\na Of course\r\nb. Sure\r\nc. Don't worry\r\nd. How much are they\r\nThe conversation below for question number 9-11\r\nRoger . Hey, Rudi ! Let's play basketball today, shall we?\r\nRudi : Oh no, not today. Sorry. Maybe tomorrow.\r\nRoger \u00b7 What's the matter?\r\nRudi I'm not feeling very well. I've got a beadache.\r\nRoger; Oh sorry to hear that. Here. Take this. You should take an spirin\r\nRudi\r\n\u2022 Er. Ok.\r\n9. What does Roger want to do ?\r\na. Play basketball\r\nb. Reads book\r\nc. Camping\r\nd. Playing football\r\n10. What does Roger give to Rudi?\r\na. A baskztball\r\nb. An aspirin\r\nC. A sboes\r\nd. A medicine\r\n11. Who take the aspirio ?\r\na Roger\r\nb. Rudi\r\nc. Sinta\r\nd. Budi\r\n12. The students go to school...... (setiap hari)\r\na. Every day\r\nb. Every Sunday\r\nc. Tomorrow\r\nd. Yesterday\r\n13. My living room is not.......(besar), but I am happy.\r\na. Small\r\n6. Big\r\nc. Beautiful\r\nd. Cheap\r\n\r\ntolong di bantu jawabanya\r\ntrimakasih\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>6. a. they are</p><p>7. stationery store</p><p>8. d. how much are they?</p><p>9. a. play basketball</p><p>10. b. an aspirin</p><p>11. b. Rudi</p><p>12. a. every day</p><p>13. b. big</p><p></p><p>semoga terbantu ya\u270c</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "write-two-sentences-expressing-what-is-happening-around-you-a-b-378",
            "question": "Write two sentences expressing what is happening around you\r\nA.\r\nB.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. many weddings</p><p>B. always stuck</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "if-hehe-will-get-hiher-aim-271",
            "question": "If he...he will get hi/her aim\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>her</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "teks-iklan-mie-goreng-dalam-bahasa-inggris-720",
            "question": "Teks iklan mie goreng dalam bahasa inggris\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>fried noodle ad text kek gitu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>B.indonesia: Iklan mie goreng</p><p></p><p>Terjemahan b.inggris: Fried noodle advertisement</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p></p><h3>Semoga bermanfaat dan membantu;)</h3>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "2-the-girls-are-watching-movie-in-the-cinema-547",
            "question": "2. (+)The girls are watching movie in the\r\ncinema.\r\n(-)..\r\n(?)...\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>(-) The girls aren&#039;t watching movie in the cinema</p><p>(?) Are The girls watching movie in the\n</p><p>cinema?</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "taj-mahal-of-india-isthan-candi-prambanan-of-indonesia-249",
            "question": "Taj mahal of india is...than candi prambanan of indonesia",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Taj mahal of india is <strong>bigger</strong> than candi prambanan of indonesia</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Jawaban dicetak tebal dan menggunakan bentuk komparatif dengan kata sifat (Adjective) satu suku kata sehingga untuk membentuk komparatif harus ditambahkan akhiran -er, menjadi is bigger than. Jawaban tidak mutlak is bigger than, tetapi bisa juga is smaller than atau kata lain yang dianggap lebih sesuai dan lebih valid berdasarkan data pengukuran matematis.</p><p>Semoga membantu ya.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "what-is-the-climax-of-the-strory-true-friends-once-upon-a-time-909",
            "question": "What is the climax of the strory?    True Friends\r\n\r\n Once upon a time, there were two close friends who were walking through the forest together. They knew that anything dangerous can happen any time in the forest. So they promised each other that they would always be together in any case of danger.\r\n\r\n Suddenly, they saw a large bear getting closer toward them. One of them climbed a nearby tree at once. But unfortunately the other one did not know how to climb up the tree. So being led by his common sense, he lay down on the ground breathless and pretended to be a dead man.\r\n\r\n The bear came near the one who was lying on the ground. It smelt in his ears, and slowly left the place because the bears do not want to touch the dead creatures. After that, the friend on the tree came down and asked his friend that was on the ground, \"Friend, what did the bear whisper into your ears?\" The other friend replied, \"Just now the bear advised me not to believe a false friend.\"\r\n\r\n Moral of the Story- A true friend in need is a friend indeed",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Apa klimaks dari cerita tersebut?</p><p></p><p>Teman sejati</p><p></p><p>Alkisah, ada dua orang sahabat yang sedang berjalan bersama di hutan. Mereka tahu bahwa segala sesuatu yang berbahaya dapat terjadi kapan saja di hutan. Jadi mereka berjanji satu sama lain bahwa mereka akan selalu bersama dalam keadaan bahaya apa pun.</p><p></p><p>Tiba-tiba, mereka melihat seekor beruang besar mendekat ke arah mereka. Salah satu dari mereka memanjat pohon terdekat sekaligus. Namun sayangnya yang satunya tidak tahu bagaimana cara memanjat pohon tersebut. Jadi dibimbing oleh akal sehatnya, dia berbaring di tanah dengan terengah-engah dan berpura-pura menjadi orang mati.</p><p></p><p>Beruang itu mendekati orang yang terbaring di tanah. Itu tercium di telinganya, dan perlahan meninggalkan tempat itu karena beruang tidak mau menyentuh makhluk mati. Setelah itu, teman di pohon itu turun dan bertanya kepada temannya yang ada di tanah, \"Teman, apa yang dibisikkan beruang ke telingamu?\" Teman yang lain menjawab, \"Baru saja beruang itu menasihati saya untuk tidak mempercayai teman palsu.\"</p><p></p><p>Moral of the Story- Teman sejati yang membutuhkan adalah teman sejati.</p><p></p><p>Semoga membantu^^</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "make-your-own-paragraph-about-your-activity-in-the-past-start-fr-886",
            "question": "Make your own paragraph about your activity in the past. start from 'a long time ago'\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>a long time ago i was playing in the backyard. playing with mud and grass to be exactly, i ended up playing for 2 hours straight and imagining things, when i got up my whole outfit was under the mud. i had to take a shower</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "2-mention-three-the-functions-modal-verbs-of-can-and-could-write-893",
            "question": "2 Mention three the functions modal verbs of CAN and COULD!    Write down three sentences of CAN and COULD\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>makanya toxix tiap hari</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "i-am-can-fly-639",
            "question": "I am........ can fly\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>bird</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>.................. </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Mine Craft  creative mode</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "9-please-return-my-jacket-soon-okay-the-underlined-word-means-a-398",
            "question": "9. Please return my jacket soon. Okay    The underlined word means\r\nA Let something drop\r\nB Give something back\r\nC. Make something better\r\nD Send something home\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>B. give something back</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>return berarti mengembalikan</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p> B give something back</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>it says return so it Means give something back bc</p><p>return =give back or something else whatever</p><p>smoga membantu :/</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}